Emma Brown

J +34-657145963 **≥** emma_brown@gmail.com

Ponferrada, León

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Human resources professional with over fifteen years of experience. Accustomed to addressing the changing needs of an office. Adept in various software applications and office equipment. I am looking to continue developing and the role of a receptionist is an excellent fit for my skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

•Human Resources Manager

Norfolk Souther Corporation, Norfol, Virginia

09/2008 - 02/2023

- Led new talent acquisition and recruitment processes for new full-time hires.
- Administered company-wide compensation and benefit plans.
- Managed the firm's organizational structure, responsibilities, and staffing levels.

•Human Resources Generalist

The Port of Virginia, Norfolk, Virginia

07/2007 - 06/2008

- Handled recruitment processes.
- Administered company-wide compensation and benefit plans.

Office Clerk

Apria Healthcare, Norfolk, Virginia

04/2006 - 06/2007

- Anwered calls and scheduled appointments.
- Sorted incoming mail and handled outgoing mail.
- Processed bills and handled other confidential documents.
- Typed and edited memos and reports.

EDUCATION

•Associate of Arts, Tidewater Community College, Norfolk, Virginia

2005

•High School Diploma, Granby High School, Norfolk, Virginia

2001

LANGUAGES

English: native, Spanish: intermediate (B1), French: beginner (A2).

SKILLS

HR Software(Oracle)

MS Office(Word, Excel, PowerPoint)

Data entry

Typing (60 WPM)

People management

Recruitment